(Howard:)So nice you could join me this evening.
You're looking lovely as always.
(Katee Sackhoff:)Thanks, Howard.
(Katee Sackhoff:)Always nice to be part
of your masturbatory fantasies.
(Howard:)Come on, Katee,
don't make it sound so cheap.
(Katee:)I'm sorry. Fiddling with yourself
in the bathtub is a real class act.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
So, ahem, shall we get started?
(Katee:)Sure, but can I ask you
a question first?
You wanna play Cylon and colonist?
No, I wanna know why
you're playing make-believe with me...
(Katee:)...when you could be out
with a real woman tonight.
(Howard:)-You mean Bernadette?
-No, I mean Princess Leia.
(Katee:)Of course I mean Bernadette.
(Katee:)She's a wonderful girl
and she really likes you.
(Howard:)-I know, but she's not you.
-I'm not me.
(Katee:)The real me is in Beverly Hills
with a tall, handsome rich guy.
(Howard:)-Really? Tall?
-Six-four.